我已经上了十次厕所
That was the 10th time I've peed here.
你也跟我们说了十次
It's also the 10th time you've told us.
抱歉，你们一定听得很烦
Sorry,it must be hard to hear.
你以为三个宝宝在你的膀胱上 蹦蹦跳跳比较好玩吗
It's easier having babies playing "Bring in Da Funk" on your bladder!
我真是受够怀孕了
I am so sick of being pregnant. God!
我睡不着，除非睡床上 但是又会痛，等于睡不着
I can't sleep,except on my back,which hurt. So I can't sleep.
我唯一的乐趣来自咖啡 但因为我怀孕我只能喝低咖啡因的
My only happiness is from a cup of coffee...which is decaf because I'm pregnant!
菲比，你要吃饼干吗？
You want a cookie?
谢谢你
Thank you so much!
你的情绪起伏还好吗？
So,honey,how are those mood swings coming?
我还没有这个困扰
I haven't had any yet.
本集播出：“史上最差伴O”
The One with the Worst Best Man Ever
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
嘿
Hey,guys.
这就是戒指
All right,here's the ring.
我愿意，我愿意，千百个愿意
Yes,yes! A thousand times,yes!
单身派对有想法了吗？
Any ideas for the bachelor party?
托管戒指办派对前 应该先选个伴O吧？
Before rings and bachelor parties,you have to decide who your best man will be.
真尴尬，尴尬尴尬
Oh,it's awkward.
我已经找钱德了
I already asked Chandler.
什么？你上次结婚他就当过了
He got to do it at your first wedding.
我以为你会了解 我们认识比较久
I figured you'd understand. I've known him longer.
拜托啦，我没有兄弟 我永远都没机会了
I don't have any brothers. I'll never be a best man.
你可以当我的伴O
You can be the best man when I get married.
我没机会了啦
I'll never get to be a best man!
等一下
Wait,wait.
我让你当两次 你一次也不让我当？
So you'll be my best man twice,and I won't be yours at all?
你当然可以当我的伴O
Of course,you can be my best man.
那我呢？你说我可以当
-What about me? You said I could.
我又没有要结婚
-I'm not getting married!
那是科幻小说要挑战的题材
It's a question for science-fiction writers.
你居然不找我 你怎么可以不找我？
I can't believe it's not me.-How could it not be me?
我又没要…我又没要…
-I'm not even
好，够了
You know what? That's it.
乔伊，从现在起你当我的伴O
From now on,Joey will be my best man.
太好了！不过真的替你羞愧
Yes!Shame about you,though.
别闹 怎么了？
-Stop it. -What?
有个宝宝在踢 那不是好事吗？
One of the babies is kicking.
不是踢我，是踢另一个宝宝
That's a good thing.It's not kicking me. It's kicking another baby.
别逼我进去
Don't make me come in there!
有大碗可以借给我吗？
Do you have a big bowl I can borrow?
台子下面有一个
There's one under the cabinet.
干嘛？ 我们明天要开派对，回见
-Why do you need it? -We're having a party tomorrow night.
你们有打算要邀请我们吗？
-Are you planning on inviting us?
没有，回见
-No. Later!
崔比亚尼，给我滚回来
Get your ass back here,Tribbiani!
荷尔蒙
Hormones.
菲比的意思是 你们开派对怎么不找我们？
How come you're having a party and we're not invited?
那是罗斯的单身派对 所以呢？
-It's Ross' bachelor party. -So?
你们是单身汉吗？
Are you bachelors?
不是 你们是脱衣舞娘吗？
Are you strippers?
不是 那就抱歉了
Then you're not invited.
那你们也别想参加我们的派对
Then you're not invited to our party either.
什么派对？
What party?
菲比的宝宝洗礼会
Phoebe's baby shower.
洗礼会？ 听起来就很不想参加，回见
Baby shower? That so doesn't sound like something I want to do.
你们居然要帮我办派对
I can't believe I'm going to have a party.
太棒了，派对耶
That's so great. A party!
我也不知为什么哭
I don't know why.
在酒方面我的计划是
This is what I got going for the party liquor-wise.
买一大堆酒 很好
-Get a lot of liquor. -Great.
至于邀请名单有你、我、钱德
In terms of the invite list,I got you,me and Chandler.
我会请甘瑟 因为我们讨论得很大声
I'll invite Gunther because we're talking pretty loud.
我会去
I'll be there.
派对是为你办的 但我想限制博物馆怪人的数量
I know it's your party...but I'd like to limit the number of museum geeks.
那就别找人类学家 找搞恐龙的就好
Let's not invite any anthropologists. Just the dinosaur dudes.
好，还得买一些汽水酒
We'll need a six-pack of Zima.
你们在干嘛？
Hey,what are you doing?
跟我的伴O筹划我的单身派对
Just planning my bachelor party with my best man.
祝你们办得比上次好
Good luck trying to top the last one.
不难，因为这次 不会办在必胜客的地下室
It won't be that difficult since this one won't be...in the basement of a Pizza Hut.
我是罗斯，必胜客配不上我
I'm Ross,I'm Ross. I'm too good for the Hut.
我得去接儿子，看样子没问题
I gotta go pick up Ben. Everything sounds great.
总之不要太疯，大家聚聚打牌
Keep it on the mellow side. A few guys hanging out.
不要找脱衣舞娘，好吗？ 没问题
-No strippers or anything. -You got it.
待会见
See you later.
好好办不能疯的派对吧
Have fun planning your mellow party.
会有脱衣舞娘，他没说不要
There will be strippers. He didn't say anything about no strippers.
他刚就说不要
He just said,"No strippers."
我当做没听到
I chose not to hear that.
你看我买了什么
Look what I got,look what I got!
居然有这种童装
They make these for little people!
给乡下小孩穿的
Little Village People.
你看这件，我最喜欢这件
Look at this one. This is my favorite.
太可爱了 菲比一定会很喜欢打扮他们
That is so sweet.Phoebe will love dressing them.
但到时替他们打扮的不是她
Except she won't be the one who gets to dress them.
因为她不能把宝宝留着
She won't get to keep the babies.
天哪 这真是最令人沮丧的洗礼会
My God,we are throwing the most depressing baby shower!
除非送她产后可以用的礼物
Unless we give her all gifts she can use after her pregnancy.
像普通咖啡，龙舌兰 一整盒烟
Like regular coffee. Tequila!-A carton of cigarettes!
她又不抽烟 心意最重要
-She doesn't smoke.-It's the thought that counts.
好主意 还有她一直想要的皮裤
-It's a great idea.And those leather pants she's always wanted!
她一定会很高兴
She'll love that!
这是什么玩意？
What the hell is this?
送我2个月后才能用的礼物 我的心情会好吗？
You thought it'd make me feel better?To give me something I can't use for two months?
烂透了
This sucks!
这是谁送的？
-Who gave me this? -Well,l
我…我…她们说你喜欢
They told me you like them.
好吧，我错了 这是我收过最棒的礼物
All right,then I'm wrong. It's a great gift. The best present I ever got!
下一个礼物呢？ 我们都没带
What's my next present?We don't have anything.
好吧，送礼会结束
All right,fine,then this is over.
真是的…放什么汽球
Balloons!
对了，那个脱衣舞娘…
-Listen,about the stripper.... -Yeah?
叫得好
Good call!
知道下次要找谁办了吧
So I'll be hosting your next bachelor party?
我希望这是我的最后一次
Joey,I'm kind of hoping this will be my last one.
请注意
A little announcement.
我决定我的伴O 是我最要好的朋友甘瑟
I've decided that my best man is my best friend Gunther.
我姓什么？
What's my last name?
中央咖啡馆？
Central Perk?
谢谢你没娶瑞秋
Thanks for not marrying Rachel.
甘瑟，记得拿衣服
Hey,Gunther! Don't forget your shirt.
那是什么？ 派对小赠品，你看
What are those?Little party favors. Check it out.
（98罗斯盖勒单身派对）
（伴O乔伊崔比亚尼）
请注意，我的伴O人选还空着
Just want everybody to know the position of my best man is still open.
新娘人选也是
So is the position of the bride.
很好
Great.
有一套，你的脖子沾到辣椒
Smooth,man.You got some chili on your neck.
谢谢大家，今晚很愉快
I just want to say thanks,everyone. This was great!
星期一早上见
See you guys Monday morning.
乔伊，谢了 别忘了拿衣服
-Thanks,Joey. -Don't forget your shirt.
博物馆怪胎，派对结束了
Hey,museum geeks! Party's over.
跟小姐说再见，快点
Wave bye-bye to the nice lady. There you go.
回爸妈的地下室去
Back to your parents' basement. All right.
出来吧，来
Boys,come on out. Here you go.
好可爱喔，是你养的？
Look at the birdies! Are those yours?
我不知道可以养鸡鸭当宠物
They let you keep chickens and ducks as pets?
我把鸭子训练得很好，你看
And I got the duck totally trained too.
盯着墙壁
Stare at the wall.
几乎不动
Hardly move.
白白的
Be white.
你真行
You are good at that.
今晚很愉快，派对办得很棒
I had fun tonight.-You throw one hell of a party.
谢了，很高兴认识你
-Thanks. It was great meeting you.
要是我有朋友要结婚 或是过生日、过星期二…
If any of my friends ever get married or have a birthday or a Tuesday....
那就太好了
Yeah,that'd be great.
那就再见了
So,I guess,good night.
除非你想留下来
Unless you want to hang around.
是吗？ 对，你可以跟我的鸭子玩
I'll let you play with my duck.
跳脱衣舞的
Stripper!
舞娘把戒指偷走了
The stripper stole the ring!
钱德，起床 舞娘把戒指偷走了
Chandler,get up! The stripper stole the ring!
什么？ 戒指被偷了
-What? -The ring is gone!
先让我清醒一下
Just give me a minute to wake up for this.
你把戒指弄丢了 你是最烂的伴O
You lost the ring. You're the worst best man!
不好笑，怎么办？ 我去睡觉，一切正常
This isn't funny. I go to sleep,everything's cool.
等我醒来，舞娘不见了 戒指也不见了
I wake up,the stripper's gone,and the ring is gone!
你跟她上床？ 废话
-You slept with her? -Of course!
你们两个 菲比
-Hi,guys. -Hi,Phoebe.
我想说声抱歉 我昨天在洗礼会上似乎凶了点
I wanted to apologize if I seemed a tad edgy yesterday at my shower.
荷尔蒙作祟
Just the hormones.
别这样，我们… 荷尔蒙嘛
-No,we -Hormones.
谢谢你们，你们真有心
I wanted to say thank you. It was so sweet.
你似乎好多了，太好了
You seem to be doing much better.
你现在怎样？ 很好
-How are things going? -Good.
最近的注意力都在我 你们呢？
Everything's been about me lately. So what's happening with you?
我们正在说 我不去参加罗斯的婚礼
We were just talking about me not going to Ross' wedding.
有那段过往，我可能很难面对
It just might be too hard,given the history and all that.
这让我想起当年流落街头时
This reminds me of the time when I lived on the street.
有人说我陪他上床就请我吃饭
This guy offered to buy me food if I slept with him.
这两件事哪里像？
How is this like that?
我想想…的确不像
Well,let's see. It's not really like that.
因为那才算是问题
Because that was an actual problem.
你这只是高中女生无病呻吟 没人在乎
And yours is just a bunch of high-school crap...that nobody really gives!
抱歉，我只是…
I'm sorry. I just thought
泪眼攻势来了
Here come the water works.
我已经没辄了 我打给中介站，他们不管
I called the company that sent her,and they don't care.
我打911又被吼 这还不算紧急事件吗？
I called 911 and they yelled at me. This is an emergency!
我真的很想帮忙 但我打算去看“泰坦尼克号”
I really wanna help you out,but I got plans to go see Titanic...
所以我要打911问场次
...so I've got to call 911 to find out what time it starts.
我来了
Hey,guys.
谢谢你，派对办得很棒 博物馆那伙人玩得很爽
Thanks again for last night. What a great party.The guys from work had a blast.
其中有一个没参加过单身派对
One of them had never been to a bachelor party before.
另一个没参加过派对
Another one had never been to a party before.
那个结婚戒指
So that wedding ring.
可真漂亮 漂亮吧
-Man,that is nice. -Yeah,right?
我也想买一个，要去哪里买？
I might pick one of those babies up for myself.Where might one get one of those?
那个戒指？
That ring?
我外婆刚来到这个国家时
When my grandmother first came to this country...
全身上下只有那只戒指 和一小包衣服
...that ring and the clothes on her back were all she had with her.
所以那只戒指可说是无可取代
So you might say that the ring is irreplaceable.
当然，它是我家的传家宝
Absolutely. It's been in my family for generations.
每个戴上它的新娘 都能幸福到老
Every bride who's worn it has lived a long and happy life.
所以简直算是一只魔戒
So you might say it's a magic ring.
被脱衣舞娘偷了
Yeah,the stripper stole it.
什么？
What?
你刚才说…
-What did you just
我想我听到了，他应该是说…
-I think I heard what he said.I believe it was,
“被脱衣舞娘偷了”
"The stripper stole the ring."
偷了我的戒指？我的结婚… 脱衣舞娘偷了我的结婚戒指？
My ring? My wedding ring?The stripper stole my wedding ring?
怎么会这样？
How could this happen?
原因就在于你说了 “乔伊，你来当我的伴O吧”
It all started when you said,"Joey,you be my best man!"
好，我来报警
All right. I'm going to call the cops.
我搞砸了你也不用报警捉我吧
I screwed up. But you don't have to turn me in.
不是捉你，是捉那个舞娘
-Not on you,on the stripper.
我试过了 他们说等侦破所有谋杀案再说
-I already did that.They said they'd look into it after they solve all the murders.
那就找中介
-We'll call the company that sent her.
我也试过了 他们不肯透露她的真名或电话
-I did that too.They wouldn't give me her real name.
他们说我再打去就要报警
They said if I bother them again,they'd call the police.
我说“你去啊” “就说我掉了一只戒指”
I said,"You talk to the police,you tell them I'm missing a ring."
难道一点办法也没有？
So,what are you telling me?There's nothing we can do?
怎么会这样？
-How could this happen?
罗斯，我真的很抱歉
-Look,Ross,I am so sorry.
我们可以再叫她一次 用假名把她找去我的办公室
What if we just called her...used a fake name and had her come to my office?
好像不赖，但我们得找戒指
That sounds like fun,but we got a ring to find!
菲比，你的茶
Here's your tea,Phoebe.
感觉真好
It's so good.
谢谢
Thanks.
那就好 你喜欢就好
-Good. -So glad you like it.
怎样？茶是她泡的
What? She made the tea.
不是，我刚才阵痛了
I think I just had a contraction.
什么？ 天哪
-What? -My God!
几分钟前就有一次 这次绝对错不了
I felt one a few minutes ago.That definitely was one.
你不能在这里生 男生搬走之后我还没消毒
You can't have the baby here.I haven't sterilized the apartment since the guys moved out!
没事，别怕，我来烧水撕床单
It's okay. I'll boil some water and rip up some sheets.
别紧张，可能是假性阵痛
It's probably false labor.
接近预产期会这样，去拿书来
That can happen near the end. Just get the book.
瑞秋，拿书来 书，好
-Get the book! -The book!
圣经？ 我哪知啊
-The Bible? -I don't know!
好，很好
All right. This is great.
钱德，你站到桌子后面
You get behind the desk.
但愿她一进来不会认得你 因为…她怎么会认得你
When she comes in,she won't recognize you because Well,why would she?
然后你对罗斯和我打暗号
And then you buzz Ross and l.
你是冈萨勒斯先生 我是王先生
You be Mr. Gonzales,and I'll be Mr. Wong.
不同种类的民族
Diverse.
有人叫警卫吗？
Anybody call for security?
冷静
You be cool.
好，哪位是甘瑟中央咖啡馆？
Which one is Gunther Central Perk?
乔伊
Joey.
我的戒指呢？ 我过世的外婆的结婚戒指呢？
Where's my ring? My dead grandmother's wedding ring.
你还真冷静
Way to be cool,man.
你在说什么？
What?
床头柜的丝绒盒里有只戒指 你一走它就不见了
There was a ring in a box. After you left,it was gone.
你们觉得我偷了戒指？
You think I stole some ring?
一定是你偷的 少废话，从实招来
We know you took it! Just save yourself the time and confess.
你们是哈迪兄弟（摔跤运动员）吗？
Who are you,the Hardy Boys?
我不必偷什么戒指 我1星期赚1600
I don't need to steal a stupid ring. I make $1,600 a week.
你们有人赚那么多吗？
Any of you guys make that?
嫁给我
Marry me.
我不懂，戒指整晚都在我房里
I don't get it. It was in my room all night. She didn't take it.
她没拿，我没拿，你没拿 那是谁拿的？
I didn't take it. You didn't take it. Then who did?
安静，我们在想事情
We're trying to think.
你怎么会知道是假痛？
I don't get how you know it's false labor.
你有看到宝宝出来吗？
Do you see any babies?
你感觉如何？ 还好吧
-How do you feel? -Okay,I guess.
我不知道 大概是知道快要结束了
I don't know.I know it's going to be over soon so
那不是很好吗？你说你受够了
But isn't that a good thing?You said you were sick of this.
我知道，只是通常怀孕完之后 就是当妈妈
-I know.Usually,when you're done with the pregnant thing...you get to do the mom thing.
我却会穿着皮裤喝龙舌兰
But I'll be sitting around in my leather pants,drinking tequila.
有些妈妈也会那样
Some moms do that.
那样更悲惨
That's even sadder.
我知道这么做的后果
Look,I know what I got myself into.
但他们现在在我肚子里
It's just that now that they're in me...
我仿佛了解他们
it's like I know them and
把他们送走时我会很难受
It just won't be easy when these babies have to go away.
我知道，亲爱的，但你并不会一无所有
I know,sweetie.But it's not like you won't have anything.
你会有侄子侄女 那样甚至更棒
You'll have nieces and nephews. That's even better.
少来 不，是真的
-Yeah,okay. -No,really.
你不必担心他们的大学学费
You won't be the one worrying about saving for college.
或在他们不乖时骂他们
Or yelling at them when they're bad.
或在他们吵个不停时 喂他们吃利他灵
Or putting them on Ritalin when they just won't calm down.
他们逃家会来找你 会找你讨论性的问题
You'll be the one they run away to. The one they talk to about sex.
你可以当酷阿姨菲比
You just get to be cool Aunt Phoebe.
酷阿姨菲比
Cool Aunt Phoebe.
我是蛮酷的
I am pretty cool.
还有，他们一定会爱死你
And you know what else? Are they going to love you!
他们会爱死我
They are going to love me.
谢谢你们…再次感谢
Thanks,you guys. Again.
谢什么
Oh,sweetie.Thanks.
怎么了？ 开玩笑的
What?Just kidding.
怎么了？ 天哪
Oh,my God!
又骗到了，你们真好骗
Got you again. You're so easy!
要是它有事… 乔伊，兽医说手术很简单
If anything happens to him The vet said it's a simple procedure.
所以呢？搞不好会出错 要是它没撑过来呢？
Things can go wrong. What if he doesn't make it?
它会的 要是没有呢？
-He will,Joe. -But what if he doesn't?
它是个这么好的鸭子
He's such a good duck.
我好担心它
I'm so worried about him!
有人掉了戒指吗？
Somebody lose a ring?
天哪！谢谢你，谢谢
Oh,my God! Thank you! Thank you so much!
鸭子怎么样？
How's the duck?
它很好，正在休息 你们可以去见它
Just fine. You'll see him in a bit.
太好了
Great.
罗斯，谢谢你这么冷静
-Thanks for being so cool.
没关系 当然有关系
-No,that's all right.
你找我当伴O，我却让你失望
You made me your best man and I totally let you down.
又不是你的错 当然是
-It's not your fault. -Yeah,it is.
你就不会弄丢戒指
You wouldn't have lost it.
你知道吗？罗斯，你是对的 他才应该当你的伴O
Ross,you were right. He should be your best man.
不，应该你当 别争了
-No,you should. -Don't argue.
伴O是我选的
I get to choose my best man.
你们两个我都要
I want both you guys.
真的？
Really?
你们都应该陪我站在神父面前
Both you guys should be up there with me.
你们是我的…
You two are my
有一个好朋友就够幸运的了
I'm lucky to have just one good
谢了
Thanks,man.
我去那边看看
I got to go check something,okay?
真孩子气 真没用
-What a baby! -Total wuss.
为什么外婆的戒指是给你？
-How come you're getting Nana's ring?
是妈给我的
-Mom gave it to me.
她说有个婚戒而你又可能用不上
She said something about it being a wedding ring and that you may not need...one.
我实在不必说这些
I really didn't need to tell you all that.
我觉得不公平 我一直很喜欢那个戒指
I don't really think it's fair. I mean,I've always loved that ring.
对不起，我原本会让给你 但艾蜜莉对它爱不释手
Oh,Mon,I'm sorry.I'd let you have it,but Emily's gotten really attached to it.
好吧 谢谢
Thanks.
拿去  谢谢
-Here you go. -Thanks.
你知道那个戒指 在鸭子肚子里待了2天吗？
Emily,did you know that that ring spent two days in a duck's colon?